(Howard:)All right, Raj has played
his Phantom Warlord card...
(Howard:)...and I am going to back him up
with my Strangling Vines.
Choke on that, sucker.
(Leonard:)Okay. Well, then I'll just cut your vines
with my Ruby Sword.
That's right, I did it. I cut them.
(Penny:)Um....
(Penny:)I have a question.
(Leonard:)Warlord beats troll, troll beats elf,
elf beats water sprite...
(Leonard:)...and basically everything beats
Enchanted Bunny.
Unless you have the Carrot of Power.
(Penny:)Okay, I've got another question.
(Penny:)When does this get fun?
Are we gonna talk or are we gonna play
Mystic Warlords of Ka-ah?
(Leonard:)Just play a potion card.
(Penny:)Which one?
(Sheldon:)It doesn't matter,
you can't possibly win.
(Leonard:)-Don't ruin the game.
-How could he ruin the game?
Given the cards already played, Penny can
only be holding Necromancer Potions...